

JONEL FAELDON

SR. FRONTEND ENGINEER

09171481701



• Calamba City, Laguna

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm JV. I am an object oriented experienced developer with demonstrated five years of professional experience in DevOps, Scrum, and Web development. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player and a lead with an eye for detail.

EDUCATION

POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES

BS. INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

2011 - 2015

Academic Excellence Awardee

EXPERIENCE

TREND MICRO, INC

SR. FRONTEND ENGINEER

JUN 2021 - PRESENT

Focused on IT services automation, Infrastructure as code, application development and operation with Scrum, CICD, container adoption for agile service delivery and future sustainability with security consideration on public cloud environment (AWS).

EUREKARE CORP.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

AUG 2019 - MAY 2021

Responsible for analyzing, designing and developing backend services and translate conceptual system requirements into technical data and integration requirements.

GLOBE TELECOM

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

FEB 2018 - JUL 2019

Responsible for working with internal cross team members for Konsulta MD doctors and the GTI management for automation services/platform delivery to achieve operation optimization, efficiency and business goal.

CANON BUSINESS MACHINES PHILIPPINES

APPLICATION ENGINEER

NOV 2015 - FEB 2017

Responsible for leading company's internal manual process to web application.

SKILLS

DEVELOPMENT Frontend - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, VueJS,

Vuetify, Vuex, Backend - PHP, RESTFul API, Python, MySQL

OPERATIONS CI/CD Integrations - Jenkins, Kubernetes, AWS Harbor, Docker,

Sonarqube, Smart Scan, Opsgenie, 24x7, Grafana, Thycotic, Nessus

Pro Scan, Autotesting - JEST, Nightwatch

PROCESS AUTOMATION Power Automate. Sharepoint, PowerApps, Solutions, Connectors,

Power BI, Power Virtual Agent

SOFT SKILLS Time management, Effective communication

Teamwork, Creativity, Focus, Leadership, Visionary

REFERENCE

Winston Carmelo Mid Developer | Team Lead

09057133380

Marion Balba Web Developer

09171231188